 {

      "category":
            "Sports",
      "questions":
          [
            {
               "answer": "1986",
               "question": "In which year did Maradona score a goal with his hand?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Sumo Wrestling",
               "question": "What is the national sport in Japan?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "80 Minutes",
               "question": "How many minutes is a rugby match?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Greece",
               "question": "In which country were the first Olympic Games held?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Two players",
               "question": "How many players are on each side of the net in beach volleyball?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Replace it",
               "question": "What should you do in swordplay when you break your saber?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Only one",
               "question": "How matches did Mohammed Ali lose in his career?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Fifty meters",
               "question": "How long is an Olympic swimming pool?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The number 501",
               "question": "At what number does one begin when playing Darts?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Renault",
               "question": "Which car won Fernando Alonso his first tittle in Formula 1 with?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Lance Armstrong",
               "question": "Who was the champion of the Tour de France from 1999 to 2005?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Eddy Merckx",
               "question": "Which cyclist was also called the cannibal?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Six players",
               "question": "How many players has a hockey team got on the ice?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Barcelona",
               "question": "What was the Olympic city of 1992 ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Azteca Stadium in Mexico city",
               "question": "What is the largest stadium in the world ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Billiards and ping-pong",
               "question": "Which two sports are practiced on a green table ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Brazil",
               "question": "In which country is the Interlagos F1-circuit ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Camp Nou",
               "question": "What is the name of the Barcelona football stadium ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Atlanta",
               "question": "Where were the Olympic Games held in 1996 ?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Red devils",
               "question": "What is the nickname of the Belgian national soccer team?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "The black ball",
               "question": "Which ball is worth the most points in English snooker?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Fast Flo",
               "question": "Which nickname has Florence Griffith got?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Asana",
               "question": "What is called a yoga posture?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Tennis",
               "question": "In which sport can you win the Davis Cup?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Pilates",
               "question": "Which popular fitness method was invented by a German?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Seven times",
               "question": "How many times has Michael Schumacher been a Formula 1 champion?"
             }
          ]
    }